HAIKAL AZMI

Junior Web Developer

hycarl.me.career@gmail.com / +60172037953

Hi, for now, I am currently an Intern for Kaodim Sdn Bhd, as a Junior Web Developer [Front-End] and I have been as a QA Engineer Intern here for the past 3 months.

The job scope is assisting with the development of web product features including user and internal platforms. Develop efficient and reusable front-end systems and abstractions. Build and prioritize user-friendly interface and experiences across all web products, optimized for different web clients in collaboration with the Design and Product teams. Leverage development best practices and support continuous learning initiatives including code and peer review practices and lastly, assist with tasks for web and mobile QA processes. [Front End Developer]

The job scope is quite simple which is to ensure the quality of the application, which I have to check for bugs, errors and identify users' problems, and running test cases so that I can come out with suggestions for the backend to fix those issues. [QA Engineer]

Currently, I'm interested in React, JQuery, Express, and MongoDB to strengthen myself in this world of programming. I am a junior web developer for the past 3 years (freelance) and with that, I've learnt a lot about HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL and also PHP (University) and now, while I am in Kaodim as a front-end developer, I am learning ReactJS, Ruby on Rails, and Slim languages.

I have successfully created a system for UTHM in order to enhance their registration experiences from traditional way (papers) to modern way (online system) and created a small web project for Kaodim which is a to-do list to connect the interns and their supervisor.

I'm doing freelance in developing websites in my leisure time to get as many experiences as I can and I am looking forward to exploring new things. I'm also open to any freelance jobs regarding web development, I am keen to get the experiences, hence make myself better in this field, in the future.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere



WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Kaodim (Present) Freelance - Remote

January 2018 to Present

I've done projects regarding web development, from full-stack to back-end and front-end. I'm currently in React but basic of web development already used to

Freelance

2017 to Present

Video and poster editor

Certified Facilitator

Sahabat YADIM

2016 to Present

involved over 100 programs

QA Engineer

Kaodim Sdn Bhd - Damansara

September 2019 to January 2020

Responsible for assessing the quality of specifications and technical design documents in order to ensure timely, relevant and meaningful feedback. I'm involved in planning and implementing strategies for quality management and testing.

Sign Language Teacher

Malaysian Relief Agency (MRA)

2016 to 2017 NGO activity

Technology Advisor, part time

Mac City Sdn Bhd

2016 to 2016

Musician, performing

ASIS Caklempong Team

2014 to 2016

for various programs



EDUCATION

Diploma in Information Technology in Information Technology

Universiti Tun Hussein Onn Malaysia

2017 to 2019

Pure Science

Alam Shah Science School - Kuala Lumpur, MY

2012 to 2016

Bandar Tun Hussein Onn Primary School

2006 to 2011



SKILLS

- React (Less than 1 year),
- PHP (3 years),
- HTML + CSS (3 years),
- MySQL (3 years)
- Selenium WebDriver IO (6 months)
- Java (3 years)
- JavaScript (2.5 years)
- Jira (1 year)
- Python (Less than 1 year)



LINKS

https://github.com/HycarlDev

https://stackoverflow.com/users/12174975/hycarldev



ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

COMPETENCES

- Designing websites
- Teaching English
- Handling programs and join NGO(s)
- Proficient in computer languages
- Active in eSports (CSGO)